Chandan, tell me
what two conviction traits will you give at this time, you want to change it,
healthy,
a strange city, many spots we are discussing
and which is a little different from friends, now
we are selecting the wound because the market
midcap and selective store specific is
giving very good momentum, so the
low of Balrampur Chini will return, you will see that there is
very good momentum in the sugar stock and its
weekly candle is quite impressive at that time and the
store quality is moving on its multiple business,
so the advice to buy in Balrampur Chini
and the price setup that has been formed is a
consolidation breakout in the daily and weekly chart, a
rally scooter of 10-12 cents should be
formed, so the
advice to buy in Balrampur Chini, 347 will be the stop loss here,
375-376 will be the target here, the
second trail is on ICICI,
see this, the consolidation of the last few days is on and it
seems that the government will be formed,
in the daily chart it is
repeating the John of 1520 again and again for the last four consecutive days
And a serving glass of it is being
prepared to pass it to them, so
in such a life, buying advice is 1520 with
stoploss above 1616 E
Shravan should be hanged soon by
participating in the fitting on your skin